As it shows, I got a ton done, like an unbelievable amount done.
This is the closed PR's in Lakebed where, reminder, I'm still the only contributor.
I have not forced this project onto my team yet.
They don't deserve the slop.
It's cleaning up fast.
Thank you, Fable.
But all of these PR's were done in literally two to three days.
The sheer volume of work here, especially if you're looking at the ones that actually merged
like this pile here. It's like I think 11 or 12 PRs that merged all not just in one day,
but from one thread. And I keep going and I'm on page two. We're still in things from
two days ago. Then there's a four day ago, one five days ago, then a huge jump to two weeks
because I was just not really feeling it. When I lost access to this model, I tried to
run around in circles and get the best stuff I could out of Opus, but it wasn't at the
the bar I needed to ship.
It what ended up happening is in this particular project,
Lakebed, I had a bunch of these PR stack up of work
that was like 50 to 80% complete,
but I didn't like the SDK changes it made.
I didn't really have confidence in the implementation,
including it up would just take too long.
And the result was that I kept having ideas,
I kept making PRs, and they kept sitting there doing nothing.
I probably had 20 or 30 PRs just sitting in this repo,
not moving, and the project has been sitting there
as a result, and I don't like that.
I really want to ship Lakebed.
I've talked about what Lakebed is in some other videos.
I don't want to bog you down the details
until I actually have it launched.
I haven't earned the right to market this yet.
I want it done.
So we'll do that later.
But I want to talk about the workflows
that got me this far in the project,
as well as some of the cool things I'm doing
on other projects that I've been working on.
I'm going to start in a weird place here,
but I promise it will help.
I'm going to start with min-maxing tips
and like cost reduction things
in order to make sure that when you adopt this workflow,
you don't immediately bankrupt yourself,
because if you were to go to the second half of this video
and skip straight to that part, it will be expensive.
That's what I did in the first three days.